keywordcountry.com 2016-01-30

# Privacy Policy, Keyword Country | www.keywordcountry.com

Keyword Country has the following Privacy Policy with regard to the information gathered on web pages hosted by Keyword Country. Such information is received by Keyword Country. 

The terms "we" and "us" refer to Keyword Country. 

## The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all the information collected on the Keyword Country website or submitted to Keyword Country at any time.

Personally Identifiable Informationâ€”When visiting Keyword Country and signing up for or using Keyword Country services, you may choose to supply Keyword Country with information that identifies you personally. For End-Users, this information may include your name and contact information, gender, birth date, occupation and industry, shipping and billing information, credit card numbers and other payment information, behavior patterns, purchase history, and other information. For Clients, this information may include the Client's name and contact information, the Client's website information (name, URL, visitors per day, page views per month, description, categorization), payment information, and user comments.

## The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself or others to complete the transaction for which the information is intended. Such transactions may include: administering a service, such as search, community, advertising sales, ecommerce, completing an order, replying to support requests, or contacting you if you have granted us the permission to do so. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy and the End-User Agreement, we do not share this information with outside parties without your permission except to the extent that is necessary to administer the services we offer to our Clients and End-Users, or to comply in responding to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal proceedings.

From time to time, we also use the information you provide about yourself or others to inform you of the additions or improvements made to the Keyword Country services. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways or for reasons unrelated to the ones described above without providing an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

## Our Commitment to Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures reasonably designed to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Personnel who have access to our database are trained to maintain and secure all information. 

## How Can You Access or Update Your Information

Clients can access their personally identifiable information (that Keyword Country collects online and maintains) by logging on to their password-protected account and selecting "Edit My Profile." 

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your information. 

## How to Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please [Contact Us](http://www.keywordcountry.com/contact/)
